import moment from 'moment';

const m1 = moment([2007, 6, 1]);
const m2 = moment();
const diff = moment.duration(m2.diff(m1));

export default {
  personality: 'MultiplayerGames',
  personalityId: 3,
  conversations: [
    {
      id: '1',
      parentId: '',
      question: `What is your favourite multiplayer game?`,
      answer:
        'My favourite online multiplayer game is Dota 2',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2',
      parentId: '',
      question: "How long have you been playing online games?",
      answer: `I have been playing online games for the last ${diff.years()} years`,
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '3',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'Have you won any tournaments?',
      answer: 'Yes, some of them',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'How long can you play games continuously?',
      answer:
        "The longest I have been playing a game would be 26 hours",
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '5',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'Do you ever rage on your teammates?',
      answer:
        'Yes, if they make mistakes',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '6',
      parentId: '',
      question: "Did you ever rage quit?",
      answer:
        'No I don\'t do that stuff',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '7',
      parentId: '',
      question: "Have you ever held a world record?",
      answer:
        'No....',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '8',
      parentId: '',
      question: "Have you ever tried single player games?",
      answer:
        'Yes, I have played many single player games',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '9',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'Do you have a professional team?',
      answer:
        "No, we disbanded after college",
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '10',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'Which game do you enjoy the least?',
      answer:
        "I find Call of Duty the least enjoyable game",
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '11',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'Are you a noob?',
      answer:
        "I think you're one of them",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '12',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'Do you also play mobile games?',
      answer: 'Rarely...',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '1-1',
      parentId: '1',
      question: "Which one is your favourite hero?",
      answer: 'I like playing many heroes based on the situation',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-1',
      parentId: '1',
      question: 'What\'s your win rate?',
      answer:
        'You can check it on my Steam ID',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '3-1',
      parentId: '1',
      question: 'Are you a noob?',
      answer: "My skills would be greater than your entire team",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '4-1',
      parentId: '1',
      question: 'I don\'t like Dota 2',
      answer:
        "Perhaps you should play Candy Crush",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-2',
      parentId: '2',
      question: "That\'s a long time",
      answer:
        'It sure is...',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-2',
      parentId: '2',
      question: 'Did you start playing games as you were born?',
      answer:
        "Maybe....",
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-2',
      parentId: '2',
      question: 'Have you ever tried going outside your house and breath some air?',
      answer: 'Never...., I prefer to remain inside my home',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '4-2',
      parentId: '2',
      question: 'So, you are really a noob!',
      answer: 'No .....!',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-3',
      parentId: '3',
      question: 'Which tournaments have you won?',
      answer: 'I have won TI, and Dota Majors...',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-3',
      parentId: '3',
      question:
        'Is it easy to get into the tournament?',
      answer: 'You just need skills or you won\'t qualify noob',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-3',
      parentId: '3',
      question: 'What is the largest prize money that you received?',
      answer:
        'I have received over a million dollars',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '4-3',
      parentId: '3',
      question: 'You\'re lying',
      answer: "Of course noob",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-4',
      parentId: '4',
      question: 'That\'s a lot of dedication',
      answer:
        'It\'s not dedication, just interest',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-4',
      parentId: '4',
      question:
        'Do you not eat or drink?',
      answer: 'I do that once I die in the game!',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-4',
      parentId: '4',
      question: 'Do you not feel sleepy?',
      answer:
        'Sometimes...',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4-4',
      parentId: '4',
      question: 'You\'re lying',
      answer: 'No.....!',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-5',
      parentId: '5',
      question: "Do you also make mistakes?",
      answer: 'No, I am perfect',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-5',
      parentId: '5',
      question:
        'All teammates make mistakes',
      answer: 'Some of them never learn from their mistakes',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '3-5',
      parentId: '5',
      question: 'Has anyone ever raged on you?',
      answer:
        'They dare not',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '4-5',
      parentId: '5',
      question: "That\'s a wrong method",
      answer: 'No....!',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-6',
      parentId: '6',
      question: "Wow!, that's nice to hear",
      answer: 'Thank you',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-6',
      parentId: '6',
      question: "Do you ever get frustrated in the game",
      answer:
        "Many times...",
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '3-6',
      parentId: '6',
      question: 'Rage quit is for children',
      answer:
        'I agree',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '4-6',
      parentId: '6',
      question: "I think you\'re lying",
      answer: 'I don\'t lie',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-7',
      parentId: '7',
      question: "You don\'t have a world record? What a pity",
      answer: 'I don\'t think you have either',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '2-7',
      parentId: '7',
      question: 'Do you even know how to play games?',
      answer: 'I am and will be always better than you noob',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '3-7',
      parentId: '7',
      question: 'I think you lack skills',
      answer:
        'I am perfect, I don\'t lack anything',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '4-7',
      parentId: '7',
      question: "So you\'re really a noob",
      answer: "No.....",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-8',
      parentId: '8',
      question: "What\'s you best SP game?",
      answer: 'I like Grand Theft Auto series, specifically San Andreas',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-8',
      parentId: '8',
      question: 'I think single player games are better than the others',
      answer: 'You\'re wrong, you lack the experience noob',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '3-8',
      parentId: '8',
      question: 'How many SP games have you played?',
      answer:
        'Hundreds of them....',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4-8',
      parentId: '8',
      question: "Do you suck in all those games?",
      answer: "No....",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-9',
      parentId: '9',
      question: "How many members were there in your team?",
      answer: 'There were around 15 members in our team',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-9',
      parentId: '9',
      question: 'Did your team win any professional matches?',
      answer: 'No, we practiced within ourselves',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '3-9',
      parentId: '9',
      question: 'Who was the leader?',
      answer: 'Of course, I was',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '4-9',
      parentId: '9',
      question: "Were you all noobs?",
      answer: "No....",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-10',
      parentId: '10',
      question: "Call of Duty is the best game",
      answer: 'The coming series of it, make people\'s life miserable',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '2-10',
      parentId: '10',
      question: 'Call of Duty, Modern Warfare was good',
      answer: 'Yes, that was a good game',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '3-10',
      parentId: '10',
      question: 'Don\'t you like shooting games?',
      answer: 'I like strategy, mmorpg games more',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '4-10',
      parentId: '10',
      question: "I think you're lying",
      answer: "Arrrgggg.....",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-11',
      parentId: '11',
      question: "I am not a noob",
      answer: 'Maybe, maybe not',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-11',
      parentId: '11',
      question: 'I don\'t like computer games',
      answer: 'Some people can\'t handle it',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-11',
      parentId: '11',
      question: 'I think there are noobs in every game',
      answer: 'That depends on the people\' motivation to play',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4-11',
      parentId: '11',
      question: "Noob\'s make life more difficult",
      answer: "Indeed they do!",
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '1-12',
      parentId: '12',
      question: "Great!",
      answer: 'Thanks!',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-12',
      parentId: '12',
      question: 'Which games have you played',
      answer: 'I tried Clash of Clans and Clash Royale',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-12',
      parentId: '12',
      question: 'Do you like mobile games?',
      answer: 'I guess I like the strategy games wherever they are',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4-12',
      parentId: '12',
      question: "Which one's would you recommend?",
      answer: "Can\'t say about that",
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
  ],
};
